[
    {
        "front": "かじ",
        "back": "fire",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうほうしゃ",
        "back": "fire engine",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぬれる",
        "back": "to get wet",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "（お）ゆ",
        "back": "hot weather",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "わかす",
        "back": "to boil (t.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～が）わく",
        "back": "to boil (i.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "ガス",
        "back": "gas",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "るす",
        "back": "absence",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "（かぎを）かける",
        "back": "to lock",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "もちろん",
        "back": "needless to say; of course",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "じしん",
        "back": "earthquake",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "たな",
        "back": "shelf",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "ガラス",
        "back": "glass",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "われる",
        "back": "to break (i.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～を）わる",
        "back": "to break (t.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆれる",
        "back": "to shake",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    },
    {
        "front": "こわい",
        "back": "scary",
        "chapter": "N4 C28"
    }
]